I have been robbed
and friends how are you I hope you are
doing great my name is Sundar Deepti
and today's topic is that I bought an ant
and it is going to be a year now get it
insured and I took some advance
in insurance and for which brand
I want to share with you so that
if you want to get your vehicle insured then
some points will
remain in your mind as to which advance
should be taken and which should not be taken
according to how old the vehicle is so you
invest more time I would
like to tell you friends this
insurance that I have got done
from The New India Assurance I am a Sikarwar of
Apollo and The New India Assurance for 6 years
and till now I have not faced any problem till
date I never had to
clear the insurance and somewhere you had
also seen my banking video like me
I somewhere
press a little more on government job ranged from in
comparison type so I would
like to tell you that the hint that I have got that it will cost approximately Rs.
3000 for me so if I  If I had
taken comprehensive insurance for one year and there were
no additions to it, it would have cost me almost 23,000 rupees.
But I had made some additions to it,
which is very important because this
car is this CB and
God forbid, if something minor happens to its text pencil somewhere, then there are
chances of losing a lot of money from the pocket. If you make an
insurance claim, then
I have taken some advance. I will tell you one by one in the middle.
First of all, nail depression,
which we also call G-Road,
what happens in it, friends, is that when your car meets with an
accident somewhere and you make an
insurance claim, then you do
not get your hundred percent money back. There is
70% question in the play, that insurance company
dares,
you have to clear around 20% (30%) and they give 20%, that is
its definition because the
cost of the part keeps increasing over time, so
according to that,
what happens is that you get hundred
percent value of the parts.  You don't get it.
Always notice that if you make an
insurance claim,
you have to pay some amount, be it
consumables, be it any parts
near the engine, be it any mechanical part, be
it sheet metal or any repair, so
if you don't have GP insurance, then
you have to share something in it. So
what happens in GP, ​​if any of
your parts get changed, the insurance
company NCP is in charge, then the
insurance company covers 100% of it.
Friends, if I have
taken ADAM, that is very important and there is
Return to Invoice cover, so there was a lot of
premium for this, I have taken it,
it means Return to Investment
cover, that the invoice lying in my car, for which
I bought the car,
including road tax, if the car gets
totaled tomorrow, then I will get its full
value. This is Return to
Investment cover. I have seen this mostly for
three to four years that our insurance companies are giving
you advice later, I feel that as per what
I have read, but at
present if something happens  If the vehicle faces a
total loss, then the return to
include that investment is this much amount,
I will get the entire money of the vehicle,
whereas the value of the vehicle which they have estimated right now is
around 16 lakhs, the median is
not ticked but I had seen that it is around 16 lakhs,
15 lakh 80 thousand 200, that means
you can almost assume that 16 is the
declared value
of the vehicle, but if you have taken the return to investment news, then on the
first day in the invoice, you had
money of 19 lakh 99 thousand for the vehicle along with
road tax, then you will
get that money back, if
Ramesh does anything in this, then please tell me in the comment
because I have done such a small thing that for the
first time it became so expensive, say
that my vehicle becomes around 6560 1000
and I do not even take road tax for it,
so the next point friends is that what is the
zoomable items news in this, that if the
vehicle meets with an accident then  In that,
if there are some consumables in the repair like
engine oil, nuts and bolts,
things like filters etc.
What mostly happens when you have an
accident, then you have to pay the cost of such things
from your pocket, but the
consumables in it, as I have
told you, are the things that will be covered in it, so
I have also looked a little in the description to see
what items will be there in the Bal Niketan Junior category in the gym yesterday, but
mostly,
some items are not covered in this comprehensive insurance, they are covered
in it, so now assume
that during the repair, you will not have to spend more money than yourself,
I have tried to match this thing for Rs 1
million and the next
point friends, this is my last add-on
order, engine protection cover, in this also
I have taken this damage, what is there in it is that if
your car gets pressurized during rain, water
goes into the engine side of the car
and the engine gets some damage, then
it will be covered if the car engine oil
leaks and the engine gets damaged, then
I have already insured this, I
can also get it done, so this thing
is engine protection cover,
I have provided you more information in the description,
please read it, the
advance which I did not take, the additional to bank
charges, I did not take no claim bonus
protection cover, I did not take high
value pay cover and what is the best, and
can you please tell me, and because of lots of
contents, I feel that if something of
yours gets stolen, then it might be
personal belongings cover again and
Miller, so I did not take these things, let's
assume that I practically
thought that if anything big like this gets lost in the car, then the
minimum loss will be incurred, let me
remind you once, I have taken
return to investment cover,
so I have taken responsible item cover, I have taken engine
protection cover and this product which
is nil depression, now if you take
insurance of your new car,
if your car is only two-three years old, then
you should take this highly recommended C road at least, in which there is
a back cover on the plastic as well.  And you
need to pay minimum amount when you make an
insurance claim. My
knowledge on this subject is a bit limited. I
invested a little and bought the insurance as per what I thought was right.
If I had
taken that cover, the insurance would have been
priced around Rs. 1000. So, I would like to
request you to share your knowledge
so that the knowledge of the readers can
increase further. Thank you very much
friends for watching this video.